Guide to the New York Building Congress Photographs PHOTOS.109
Tamiment Library / Wagner Archives
- Series II: Events, 1944-2008
  - Luncheon: Annual (Hotel Commodore, Includes George Meany): Prints and Contact Sheets, Apr 27, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Luncheon: John V. Lindsay, Oct 10, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Luncheon: Unidentified, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Luncheon: Contact Sheets, May 11, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Luncheon: Prints and Contact Sheets, Oct 27, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Luncheon: Ed Koch, Sep 27, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Luncheon: Annual: Gerald Ford, Apr 4, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Luncheon: Ed Koch: Prints and Contact Sheets, Oct 6, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Luncheon: Senator Daniel P. Moynihan, Sep 14, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Luncheon: First Leadership Awards (Includes Edward Koch, Arthur Levitt, Jr., and Robert Wagner, Jr.): Prints and Contact Sheets, Mar 29, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Luncheon: Richard Ravich: Prints and Contact Sheets, Oct 21, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Luncheon: Leadership Awards: Prints and Contact Sheets, Mar 28, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Luncheon: Leadership Awards: Prints and Negatives, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Luncheon: Millard, Oct 16, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Luncheon: Guy Molinari, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Luncheon: Gargano, Apr 23, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Luncheon: Gargano: Prints and Negatives, Apr 23, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Luncheon: Transportation: Prints and Negatives, Jun 1999 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Luncheon Committee Kick-Off, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Luncheon: "T and I", 2000 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Luncheon and Press Conference: Energy Report, Jan 25, 2001 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Luncheon: Kick-Off Reception (Grand Havana Hotel), undated (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Mayoral Meeting (?): Prints, Contact Sheet and Negatives, Nov 10, 1976(?) (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Membership Appreciation Event: Negatives, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - NYBC Construction Forecast Seminar (McGraw Hill Building), Nov 1987 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - NYBC - MIA [Marble Institute of America]: Five Year Plan, undated (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - NYBC Update, Nov 6, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - New Member Cocktail Party, Nov 17, 1958 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - New York Association of Realty Managers Event: Prints and Negatives, undated (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Officers Retirement Party, Sep 26, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Outing (Westchester Country Club), Jun 26, 1945 (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - Outing (North Hills Country Club), Jun 18, 1946 (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - Outing (North Hills Country Club), Jun 26, 1947 (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - Outing (North Hills Country Club), Jun 1948 (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - Outing (North Hills Country Club), Jun 23, 1949 (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - Outing (North Hills Country Club), Jun 22, 1950 (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - Outing (North Hills Country Club), Jun 22, 1950 (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - Outing (N.H.S.C.) (1), Jun 21, 1951 (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - Outing (N.H.S.C.) (2), Jun 21, 1951 (Box 7, Folder 47)
  - Outing: Outing Committee, 1951 (Box 7, Folder 48)
  - Outing (Westchester Country Club) (1), Jun 16, 1952 (Box 7, Folder 49)
  - Outing (Westchester Country Club) (2), Jun 16, 1952 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Outing (Westchester Country Club) (3), Jun 16, 1952 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Outing, 1953 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Outing (Westchester Country Club), Jun 14, 1954 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Outing (Westchester Country Club), Jun 13, 1955 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Outing (Westchester Country Club), Jun 11, 1956 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Outing, Jun 10, 1957 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Outing (Westchester Country Club), Jun 9, 1958 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Outing, Jun 15, 1959 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Outing: Outing Committee, Oct 1959 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Outing, Jun 1960 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Outing (Westchester Country Club), Jun 13, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Outing (Westchester Country Club), Jun 10, 1962 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Outing (Westchester Country Club), Jun 10, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Outing: Outing Committee, Sep 1963 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Outing, Jun 22, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Outing, Jun 28, 1965 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Outing, Jun 13, 1966 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Outing (Westchester Country Club), Jun 12, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Outing (Westchester Country Club), Jun 10, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Outing (Westchester Country Club), Jun 9, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Outing (Westchester Country Club), Jun 8, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Outing (Westchester Country Club), Jun 7, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Outing (Westchester Country Club), 1972 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Outing: Prints and Contact Sheets, Jun 1973 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Outing, Jun 1974 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - [Outing], circa 1976? (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Outing, Jun 16, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - [Outing], Jun 15, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Outing: Prints and Contact Sheets, Jun 28, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Outing: Prints and Contact Sheets, Jun 18, 1983 or Jun 27, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Outing: Contact Sheets, Jun 18, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Outing (1), 1985 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Outing (2), 1985 (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Outing: Contact Sheets, Jun 29, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Outing: Prints and Negatives, Jun 13, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Outing, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Outing, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Outing, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Outing, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Outing, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Outing, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Outing 1, undated (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Outing 2, undated (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Outing 3, undated (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Outing 4, undated (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Outings, 1969, undated (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Peter's Place Rededication Event: Prints and Negatives, May 24, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Presentation of Plaque to John Klenke: Prints and Negatives, May 25, 1960 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - P.W.C. Awards, Mar 16, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Reception: Peter J. Brennan, Dec 18, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Reception: George Fox Retirement, Sep 15, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Reception: Holiday: Prints and Negatives, Dec 1996 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Reception: State Legislature, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Reception: Membership Appreciation: Prints and Negatives, Sep 30, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Reception: Membership Appreciation, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Reception: Membership Appreciation (1), Nov 4, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Reception: Membership Appreciation (2), Nov 4, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Reception: C.B.B.D., Sep 24, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Reception: Membership Appreciation, Sep 2000 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Skidmore Birthday Party, Oct 16, 1950 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Skidmore Birthday Party (Hotel Baltimore), Apr 8, 1952 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Spitzer, Elliot: Event, circa 2008 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Staff [Event], circa 1999 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Surprise Party: Board of Governors Celebration of Past Presidents, Sep 29, 1955 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Times Square Event, [1998] (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Transportation Event with [Port Authority], Apr 1, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Tunnel Tour, Jan 9, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Unidentified [Awards] Event, undated (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - Unidentified Event, Apr 8, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - Unidentified Event, Jan 2000 (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - Unidentified Event: Prints and Negatives, Feb 27, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - Unidentified Event 1 (1), undated (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - Unidentified Event 1 (2), undated (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - Unidentified Event 2 (1), undated (Box 9, Folder 40)
  - Unidentified Event 2 (2), undated (Box 9, Folder 41)
  - Unidentified Event 3, undated (Box 9, Folder 42)
  - Unidentified Event 4, undated (Box 9, Folder 43)
  - Unidentified Event 5, undated (Box 9, Folder 44)
  - Unidentified Event 6 (Includes Claire Shulman), undated (Box 9, Folder 45)
  - Unidentified Event 7: Negatives, undated (Box 9, Folder 46)
  - Unidentified Event [Leadership Awards Luncheon?], undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Unidentified Event [Leadership Awards Luncheon?], undated (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Unidentified Event and Presentation 1: Prints and Contact Sheets, undated (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Unidentified Event and Presentation 2, undated (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Unidentified Event and Presentation 3, undated (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Unidentified [Formal Luncheon?] Event (1), circa 1960s - 1970s (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Unidentified [Formal Luncheon?] Event (2), circa 1960s - 1970s (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Unidentified Forum, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Unidentified Foundation Meeting: Prints and Negatives, Sep 27, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Unidentified Events, 1946-1963 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Unidentified Events, 1964 - 1979 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Unidentified Events: Negatives, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Unidentified Events, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Unidentified Events: Prints and Negatives, May 2000 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Unidentified Events (1), undated (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Unidentified Events (2), undated (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Unidentified Events (3), undated (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Unidentified Events (4), undated (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Unidentified Events (5), undated (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Unidentified Party, 1951 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Unidentified Speaker, undated (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Visit to Battery Park City Site, Mar 13, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 22)
- Series III: Portraits, 1936-1988
  - General, undated (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - General: Negatives, undated (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - A, 1971-1973, undated (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - B (Includes Styles Bridges), 1953-1974 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - C (Includes Edward Carlough and Robert Cutler): Prints and Negatives, 1945-1976 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - D (Includes Robert W. Dowling), 1953-1988 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - E, 1961-1975, undated (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - F (Includes James Farley), 1953-1974, undated (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - G, 1960-1974, undated (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - H (Includes C. J. Haggerty, Charles Haines, Averell Harriman, Wallace K. Harrison and John F. Henning), 1936-1974, undated (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - I, undated (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - J, 1941-1967, undated (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - K: Prints and Negatives, 1965-1977, undated (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - L (Includes William L. Lauren, Arthur Levitt, Jr., and John V. Lindsay), 1962-1974 (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - M (Includes George Meany, Vice Admiral Ben Moreel, and Robert Moses), 1936-1975, undated (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - N (Includes Richard Nixon and Lauris Norstad), 1964-1971, undated (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - O (Includes William O'Dwyer), 1946-1975, undated (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - P, 1965-1975, undated (Box 10, Folder 40)
  - R (Includes Richard Ravitch and Nelson Rockefeller), 1947-1950, undated (Box 10, Folder 41)
  - S (Includes Emil Schram, Louis Skidmore and Cardinal Francis Skidmore), 1941-1979 (Box 10, Folder 42)
  - T (Includes Bertram Tallamy, Thomas Thacher, Austin Tobin and John Tunney), 1936-1974 (Box 10, Folder 43)
  - U, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 44)
  - V, 1966, undated (Box 10, Folder 45)
  - W (Includes Robert F. Wagner, Jr., Robert Weaver, Casper Weinberger, Grover Whalen and Malcolm Wilson), 1959-1977 (Box 10, Folder 46)
  - Z, 1948, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 47)
- Series IV: Site Photographs, 1948-1974
  - Construction Sites: Slides and Negatives, undated (Box 10, Folder 48)
  - Demonstration of Honeywell Indoor Air Quality Diagnositics: Prints and Slides, undated (Box 10, Folder 49)
  - Images of Albany, NY (Aerial), Jun 14, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 50)
  - NYBC Offices (Interior), 1948-1949 (Box 10, Folder 51)
- Series V: Other Formats and Oversize, 1943-1988
  - Rolled Photograph (Fun and Frolic) [Restricted, consult Tamiment staff], Dec 18, 1952 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Rolled Photograph (Fun and Frolic) [Restricted, consult Tamiment staff], 1953 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Rolled Photograph (Fun and Frolic) [Restricted, consult Tamiment staff], 1954 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Rolled Photograph (Fun and Frolic) [Restricted, consult Tamiment staff], 1956 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Rolled Photograph (Gillroy Luncheon) [Restricted, consult Tamiment staff], undated (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Rolled Photographs (Joint Luncheon, NYBC and Producers' Council, Inc. (Hotel Baltimore); Fall Meeting of the Producers' Council, Inc.) [Restricted, consult Tamiment staff], Nov 11, 1943, Nov 29, 1944; Oct 2, 1947 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Rolled Photograph (Unidentified) [Restricted, consult Tamiment staff], undated (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Rolled Photographs (Unidentified) [Restricted, consult Tamiment staff], undated (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Rolled Photographs (Unidentified) [Restricted, consult Tamiment staff], undated (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Breakfast: Contact Sheets, undated (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - First Leadership Awards Luncheon (Grand Hyatt Hotel, Includes Ed Koch, Arthur Levitt, Jr. and RobertF. Wagner, Jr.), Mar 29, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Fun and Frolic, Dec 19, 1944; Dec 18, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Fun and Frolic: Contact Sheets, 1979; 1980 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - New York City Municipal Building, undated (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Portraits, undated (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Seminar (Grand Hyatt Hotel): Contact Sheets, undated (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Stereo Slides (1), 1952 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Stereo Slides (2), 1952 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Stereo Slides (3), 1952 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Stereo Slides (4), 1953 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Stereo Slides (5), 1953 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Stereo Slides (6), 1953 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Stereo Slides (7), 1953 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Stereo Slides (8), 1953 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Stereo Slides (9), 1953 (Box 13, Folder 9)